<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jerad&#39;s place</title>
    <link>https://jerad.xyz/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jerad&#39;s place</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 11:54:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://jerad.xyz/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>State Secret</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/post/ending_the_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/post/ending_the_story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;They heard New Zealand survived, but that was in a future that I was there.&lt;br&gt;
Now that I am not due to them spiritually calling me back to my home state, California, from Tahiti, New Zealand would not have the same protection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scanners that few the island before were part of my Kingdom. I did not return and so they have left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those hidden by state secrets, who tried to kill me the month I returned to San Diego, have now given a coordinated attack July 20th, 2021 (the 2nd) 11:00pm until midnight. Those hidden in New Zealand, locals here in California who have temporarily left the state. An Entire planet of ravers - loving each other and seeking a more awake society however using the facist chauvinist methods they are turned off by, and of course the spiritual pure and awake who were done wrong by any of those before and told that it was Jerad&amp;rsquo;s fault.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reality however, was that Jerad is still unaware of what the hell they are doing and what is going on.&lt;br&gt;
He does, however, know that there is very little he can do. Most of the big events were already done by those who play while Jerad sleeps and when they make a mistake or find a level they cannot pass, they show the video to Jerad so that he can believe he is responsible or Jerad can get them past a specific problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dead People from the future rulling the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many may have seen strange things these last few years 2012 - 2021 (2023).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, as I face my 30th+ attempt on my life I can&amp;rsquo;t take this place anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Safe in paradise mid 2019, I was living the dream. An island boy with local friends, fish and family. Then, out of now where my wife errupts about an old foe that should no longer be in our hair - &amp;ldquo;my sisters friends&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shortly afterwards, I found myself being drawn back to my homeland using spiritual methods that were used to get me back to California.
But Why&amp;hellip;. ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something big had been happening these last 9 years. Multiple times over 1 was named and 1 was sought. Each time it ended a reset was in order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the first time some guy had been selected. No one wanted this guy to lead them and they opted to not talk to him and make their own team. This goes for each person that knew about this.&lt;br&gt;
So now the resources for one group to save the species and planet was broken into multiple groups each with a member from the original group.&lt;br&gt;
All but the guy chosen to lead knew about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now comes the discussion to be had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All expecting a particular leader sought that one in order to reach the group or whom they were supposed to meet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many made it to him, however, he was never &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Now</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/post/what_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/post/what_now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;better-today&#34;&gt;Better Today&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be better today than you were yesterday. Raise the bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So you made a mistake. Anxiety, shame, worry, envy..&lt;br&gt;
You set yourself up for an easy one this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shed your skin. Put on a fresh scent and become anew yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Become a purpose lead agent for yourself.&lt;br&gt;
You must no longer be the self who failed your own potential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think of how you will be weighed.&lt;br&gt;
Who will you be on that scale?&lt;br&gt;
a bulk of waist that burnt your path to salvation.&lt;br&gt;
A few ounces of gold dust - brilliantly wisked in breath.&lt;br&gt;
Instead take your gifts and build upon them your trophy self.&lt;br&gt;
See each days wealth build upon the next.&lt;br&gt;
Success after success.&lt;br&gt;
until your opportunity comes and you are asked to step up the exchange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will be more than the weight of your life,
You will get to present the wealth of purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Media Concept</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/project/new-world-media/concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/project/new-world-media/concept/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-media-story-telling&#34;&gt;New Media Story Telling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stories play out on multiple mediums such as audio podcast, written web and mobile app, broadcast, soular spectrum. Content strategy set to optimize consumer participation and engagement as well as lifestyle (&lt;strong&gt;pronouns:&lt;/strong&gt; embodied experiencer / viewer / consumer).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-way----a-level-one-culture&#34;&gt;The Way &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; A &amp;ldquo;Level-One&amp;rdquo; Culture&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way was a methodology by which a small group of individuals could incept social progress and subconscious healing.&lt;br&gt;
A planet becomes level-one when it is completely self sufficients. All the worlds necessary energy is harvested from itself by means such as heat energy from volcanic sources, wind and tide energy. Waiste and recycling is done in such a manner that the planet does not develop an excess rate which would consume more land over time and food is produced at a rate sufficient to provide the entire population with a nutritional diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-way-was-the-idea-of&#34;&gt;The way was the idea of:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using a select group of zeitgeist sensitive individuals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who would travel together to feel for the subconscious activity of a given population&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The measurement taken would be experienced and studied&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some target or desired zeitgeist or desired direction would be agreed upon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The group would meditate on what was needed in order make the social conscious or subconscios progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Last Will and Testament - Jerad and Stephanie Acosta</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/post/will_and_testiment/last_will_and_testament/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/post/will_and_testiment/last_will_and_testament/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I, Jerad Steven Acosta and Stephanie Chong Acosta, are here writing our official Will and Testament.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where we decide what to happens with all of our stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any money, property, houses, land, animals, gold, dollars, wealth, anything and everything that is ours or is owed to us - even if we are in devbt (it does not matter we do not care what anyone says) IS TO GO TO ABSOLUTELY NO ONE. Not even our kids (real or fake or god children).
We currently have NO children. It is July 5 2021.
We first wrote this will in June of 2019.
This applies to all countries and states and worlds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want any money owed to us to go to no one - this way we are not killed or manipulated or married to anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone who tells you different is a liar and you should never trust or talk to that person EVER AGAIN. they suck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;any extra lives are not to be given or used by anyone else. Any extra bodies are not to be given or used by anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any lives that have been taken or given by other people are debt and owed to us. So if someone told or made you give them extra lives or bodies then they owe the estate of Jerad Steven Acosta and Stephanie Chong Acosta.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any lawsuit that is or has been done on behalf of Jerad Steven Acosta and Stephanie Chong Acosta cannot be given out to anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other people in the lawsuit had taken stuff on purpose in order to become sick and did this on purpose. It is easy to see where it came from and that they new.&lt;br&gt;
I have been listening to there stories the whole time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So technically and legally (spiritually and normally) there are no other people who are victems of this without being at fault as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lawsuit does not go to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyworld that broke off of this one since 1986 are stolen from us.&lt;br&gt;
It appears as though 3 to 7 Planets belonged to me.&lt;br&gt;
The martians came to go through me to Stephanie and so they could take care of you (the person they chose).&lt;br&gt;
Tell Jupiter I am not upset with him. I feel really appreciate his attempt to communicate and get to know me - I especial love and appriate his wife. She loves.. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Whole of our debt:
- What has wronged us (legally speaking)
- What has been taken from us (knowing or unknowing)
- And Anything else that has been owed to us&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not worry about any financial or other debt from this earth. Jerad Steven Acosta has been experience identity theft for a while now. Fake credit and fake credit cards have been taken out in my name by other individuals. Student Loans are frozen and were supposed to be forgiven anyways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of all the computer women (or men) that were sent for me, I never received any. They were all intercepted and did so much to try and make it. I appologize for not getting to know how to reach one, and for the ones who ended up serving someone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By now everyone on this planet has died enough times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be my first time. As of July 5, 2021 I have not died yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will handle or have our debt handdled by a higher power on each additional level (so do not believe they have paid for it or handled anything by a lower level or perspective - each Power should punish or take what is owed to us so that we may be paid for in whatever dimensions or levels of consciousness there are beyond this one).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes back or wakes up, you can trace back what everyone did, you can look at how they are connected:
&amp;ldquo;Who told Who to do something&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Who made someone do something&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;What was taken from our life, wealth, spirit,&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;any of the bodies that were given and sent for us,&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;any of the crystals or black H bodies that were sent for us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This entire life I have never soul sucked or eaten or stolen any souls or spirit, Nor has me wife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should also think that they switched our frequencies a lot so Stephanie and Jerad may have been switched a lot with each other and with other people trying to assume any of our wealth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for all that has been given to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each and everyday has been a gift. We have been so blessed and cannot begin to understand how so much was done for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really hope you can find any solace in what you did for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It must have really been something special for you to have stopped so much just for our love and romance to continue. And for so many to continue to gift us so much in spiritual and bodily wealth.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Notes Are For More Than Your Desktop And Its Surrounding Walls</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/post/my_notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/post/my_notebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The bright colorful squares with an uncanny ability to repeatedly stick to page after page after wall after desktop and then some. With an investment in the proper stationary brand-named product you can pull each and any note from surfaces to edit, adjust, remove or replace more times than there are permutations for its use. This is wonderful. It is one the first aspects that allows these products to transcend their stationary label and garner a cult following in business, art and home crafts circles alike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the purposes of this article I would like to share how I use the paper swiss army knife in my everyday notebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I, as should everyone, carry around a small paper notebook for a myriad of uses: jotting down notes, quick TODO lists, phone numbers and names of people I may meet, grocery lists, uses uncountable. I am an absolute digital native. I used to wait in lines to get the newest iPhone models, I have an app for everything and develop apps for myself when I can find the excuse in a need. I even jot down my thoughts and opinions on a digitized journal which is posted online via this website. Yet still, I carry an analogue, handwritten in, paper notebook wherever I go - and I insist everybody else do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For reasons that go beyond the scope of this blog post writing notes by hand, jotting ideas down on paper, building lists with a pen and pad, even if they are migrated over to a digital task management application shortly thereafter, writing by hand is the subconscious thought of kinesthetic body processes. And just like linguistic, communication oriented thought, subconscious processes are instrumental to its ability to so concisely orchestrate the many vast networks of neurons firing into comprehensible symbolic thought recognized by the conscious mind. Take it like this, hand written notes are the, eh, handwritten notes of your mind-bodies intended action. Of course your mind and body know just what they intend to do and how they intend to do so, however, in our cluttered and stimuli rich lives it is easy to get tripped up and lose ourselves in a moment or an afternoon and find ourselves lost to our earlier goals.&lt;br&gt;
It is when you look back at your beeping of your phone to read an alert you wrote last week:&lt;br&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to bring X over to Y&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;
to which you respond with a wince followed by a:&lt;br&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Whaa&amp;hellip; t was I talking about?&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;
A note written last week that started out as a handwritten note, however, has the added reinforcement of tactile and kinesthetic muscle memory to jolt context back into place.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Ah I remember being at the grocery store learning on the cart as I wrote down this note.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Of course &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo; and yes, yes, &amp;lsquo;Y&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So please, don&amp;rsquo;t get caught up on the perceived extra effort or excess material of an analogue notebook and carry it everywhere you go. Your context rich memory content will be there to reward you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, now we can get on with the purpose of this post, to share with you how it is sticky-notes play powerful roles in my notebook and bring to life my paper toolkit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;scrum-artifacts&#34;&gt;Scrum Artifacts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a huge proponent of the agile framework. I love agile and lean everything. I even take a lean approach to the kitchen and my fashion accessories and clothing. Efficient, Powerful, Agile, Intuitive, these are all words with powerful meanings that I feel all coalesce to an archetype of why I love the results I get from Scrum which bring to the collection: Context, Reflection, Projection, Iteration, and Assimilation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of us should be familiar with Kanban boards here. For those who aren&amp;rsquo;t:&lt;br&gt;
A Kanban board is like a TODO list that moves. It starts on the left with a column titled &amp;ldquo;TODO&amp;rdquo;, then moves to the center column &amp;ldquo;DOING&amp;rdquo; then finally it proceeds to the terminal third column: &amp;ldquo;DONE&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To create and use one in your note book simply write out those three columns vertically across an open two pages in the notebook. Then, using Post-Its, write down a task item. Ideal task items are independent action oriented concepts or tasks that can be completed in and of themselves. This is important so that any single note can travel from &amp;ldquo;TODO&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;DOING&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Working On&amp;rdquo; then to &amp;ldquo;DONE&amp;rdquo; without needing other notes to travel with it.&lt;br&gt;
This is a good way to look at your errands and tasks in general. Scrum is great at forcing you to see projects and goals through independent task oriented iterations. It allows you to breakdown the biggest of problems into short tasks that can be run independent of each other - great for distributed workload across teams or for accomplishing different items in different environments such as doing &amp;ldquo;work item at the office&amp;rdquo; and doing &amp;ldquo;family items at the house&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-tables&#34;&gt;Data Tables&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love Disc Golf. So much so that I have been training, that&amp;rsquo;s not practice that is training ;-) and taking notes. When I am performing a putting exercise I track performance of my intervals on stick-notes. I use them because they stick to the tree, the ground, or even a disc, whever I need them to while I write on them or place them aside in order to putt. Afterwards, I rip the note off of whatever surface it was last and place it into my notebook. Generally it will find itself in similar company around other notes with grids of numbers and fractions representing previous scores and performance metrics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sticky-note is an amazing piece of office-ware turned cultural tapestry. So many people use them for so many things and to those who do they are absolutely essential.&lt;br&gt;
Similarly the notebook is quintessential buffer for your mind. Offloading thoughts, comments, and tasks or expanding upon concepts and ideas into coherent narratives that someday live digital lives, eternally grafting their experiences to the minds of others who keep the cycle going and jot down their thoughts on the matter in a trusty notebook - full of sticky-notes I hope..&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evidence Locker</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/post/evidence_locker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/post/evidence_locker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something happened. Something so beautiful it swept a peoples by the &amp;lsquo;-aww&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A cloud of living motherly love&lt;br&gt;
Wrapped herself about such hope and expectation&lt;br&gt;
What became was exactly what was needed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fracture, something is wrong
&amp;ldquo;no &amp;hellip; no &amp;hellip; this can&amp;rsquo;t be right..&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;something is missing&amp;rdquo;
&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The future&lt;br&gt;
It Was&lt;br&gt;
It was beautiful&lt;br&gt;
It was ..
was it
where is .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something isn&amp;rsquo;t here&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2012 end of the year
On our trip of new zealand. Traveling around the north island.
Green pastures. Shaving german rabbits. Rafting through tunnels of glowing worms. Staying on the lake. Eating Indian before bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything was so great. Adventures through webs and dinosaurs, a maze of laughter as we loved each and every moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back it was almost as if we were hunted for what we had ever since that trip.&lt;br&gt;
Radios and spiritual witchcraft of the 21st century used to bend will and lead us like a mouse to cheese.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;clues&#34;&gt;Clues&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2009 fell in love, split in two for her and started to amass grey hair at an exponential rate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone has been using my most loyal love to hurt me
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They take from me through her&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hong Kong a mistake was corrected through bringing her back to me
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In taking her memory and assets she was promised to never fail me again and expected to have me a master and be like she was in Costa Verde / La Jolla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;She returned to find god in me and instill my undying desire to protect and defend her&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We could no longer recognize each other on our next trip home
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I stubbornly left to seek out some underlying forces manipulating people in my life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wrote / am writing an application for to help your Disc Golf game</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/post/dgg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/post/dgg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Check out my new app &lt;a href=&#34;jerad.shinyapps.io/DiscGolfGrowth&#34;&gt;DGG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;passion-and-pleasure&#34;&gt;Passion and Pleasure&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve done it! I have got a creation that combines my technical expertise, cunning computational wizardry, a need to always be learning and pushing myself conceptually and technically &lt;strong&gt;WITH MY LOVE FOR DISC GOLF.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now getting something to assume the first half of the requirements is about any data application or dashboard on a halfway interesting dataset. But for sometime I have been pushing at my creative ends working to come up with a way to incorporate my urge to develop and uncover data lead insights with my passion for Disc Golf.&lt;br&gt;
I speak about it as though Disc Golf was a life-long pursuit of which I was an expert. I am actually quite novice to the sport and far from expert level performance or even knowledge. I have been playing for almost 9 months now. I started last August in the middle of COVID-19 along with so many others in the Disc Golf surge seen during COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this is perfect! What better time to find usefulness from data analytics on the acquisition of my disc golf game than during my early years. I can even carry this on to track into the mature development of my game and beyond. And it should make for an interesting time of trial, error, and data fed insights before I have time to build up an intuition for the sport.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way I plan to track and use data makes it even more appropriate. I am focusing not on the game performance itself but on the users performance during routine exercises, drills, and specific activities key to the disc golf game.&lt;br&gt;
Examples include putting drills where I record the amount of successful attempts from different distances, measuring the length of my disc golf drive with different discs, tracking my encounters with instructional information from blogs and YouTube, and - of peculiar interest to me - I will be recording a regular wellness survey to measure my emotional and physical wellbeing as they are experienced by me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check in on the status of the apps prototype as I release updates here: &lt;a href=&#34;jerad.shinyapps.io/DiscGolfGrowth&#34;&gt;DGG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am developing the application in R, using libraries like Shiny and ShinyDashboard to create a reactive web app experience on a modern Dashboard UI.&lt;br&gt;
Time and resources permitting I would like to develop a final version as a native mobile application that can be released on the Apple App Store with the likes &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.udisc.com&#34;&gt;UDisc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until then, I&amp;rsquo;ll be chucking rubber and plugging away at pulling insights from my training.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wish List</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/post/wish_list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/post/wish_list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Check out my new app &lt;a href=&#34;jerad.shinyapps.io/DiscGolfGrowth&#34;&gt;DGG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;passion-and-pleasure&#34;&gt;Passion and Pleasure&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve done it! I have got a creation that combines my technical expertise, cunning computational wizardry, a need to always be learning and pushing myself conceptually and technically &lt;strong&gt;WITH MY LOVE FOR DISC GOLF.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now getting something to assume the first half of the requirements is about any data application or dashboard on a halfway interesting dataset. But for sometime I have been pushing at my creative ends working to come up with a way to incorporate my urge to develop and uncover data lead insights with my passion for Disc Golf.&lt;br&gt;
I speak about it as though Disc Golf was a life-long pursuit of which I was an expert. I am actually quite novice to the sport and far from expert level performance or even knowledge. I have been playing for almost 9 months now. I started last August in the middle of COVID-19 along with so many others in the Disc Golf surge seen during COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this is perfect! What better time to find usefulness from data analytics on the acquisition of my disc golf game than during my early years. I can even carry this on to track into the mature development of my game and beyond. And it should make for an interesting time of trial, error, and data fed insights before I have time to build up an intuition for the sport.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way I plan to track and use data makes it even more appropriate. I am focusing not on the game performance itself but on the users performance during routine exercises, drills, and specific activities key to the disc golf game.&lt;br&gt;
Examples include putting drills where I record the amount of successful attempts from different distances, measuring the length of my disc golf drive with different discs, tracking my encounters with instructional information from blogs and YouTube, and - of peculiar interest to me - I will be recording a regular wellness survey to measure my emotional and physical wellbeing as they are experienced by me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check in on the status of the apps prototype as I release updates here: &lt;a href=&#34;jerad.shinyapps.io/DiscGolfGrowth&#34;&gt;DGG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am developing the application in R, using libraries like Shiny and ShinyDashboard to create a reactive web app experience on a modern Dashboard UI.&lt;br&gt;
Time and resources permitting I would like to develop a final version as a native mobile application that can be released on the Apple App Store with the likes &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.udisc.com&#34;&gt;UDisc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until then, I&amp;rsquo;ll be chucking rubber and plugging away at pulling insights from my training.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Study of Snail Behavior</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a free website with academia using Markdown, Jupyter, or RStudio. Choose a beautiful color theme and build anything with the Page Builder - over 40 &lt;em&gt;widgets&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;themes&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;language packs&lt;/em&gt; included!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://academia-demo.netlify.com/&#34;&gt;Check out the latest &lt;strong&gt;demo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/#expo&#34;&gt;view the &lt;strong&gt;showcase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of personal, project, and business sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#install&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Setup academia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/get-started/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Started&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/&#34;&gt;View the documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://discuss.gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Ask a question&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academia/issues&#34;&gt;Request a feature or report a bug&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updating? View the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/update/&#34;&gt;Update Guide&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/updates/&#34;&gt;Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support development of academia:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://paypal.me/cushen&#34;&gt;Donate a coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/cushen&#34;&gt;Become a backer on Patreon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redbubble.com/people/neutreno/works/34387919-academia&#34;&gt;Decorate your laptop or journal with an academia sticker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://academia.threadless.com/&#34;&gt;Wear the T-shirt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academia/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academia/master/academia.png&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key features:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Page builder&lt;/strong&gt; - Create &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/page-builder/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;widgets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;elements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit any type of content&lt;/strong&gt; - Blog posts, publications, talks, slides, projects, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create content&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/jupyter/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jupyter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/install/#install-with-rstudio&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RStudio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin System&lt;/strong&gt; - Fully customizable &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/themes/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;color&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;font themes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display Code and Math&lt;/strong&gt; - Code highlighting and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/LaTeX/Mathematics&#34;&gt;LaTeX math&lt;/a&gt; supported&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrations&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;a href=&#34;https://analytics.google.com&#34;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://disqus.com&#34;&gt;Disqus commenting&lt;/a&gt;, Maps, Contact Forms, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beautiful Site&lt;/strong&gt; - Simple and refreshing one page design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry-Leading SEO&lt;/strong&gt; - Help get your website found on search engines and social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Media Galleries&lt;/strong&gt; - Display your images and videos with captions in a customizable gallery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mobile Friendly&lt;/strong&gt; - Look amazing on every screen with a mobile friendly version of your site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-language&lt;/strong&gt; - 15+ language packs including English, 中文, and Português&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-user&lt;/strong&gt; - Each author gets their own profile page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Pack&lt;/strong&gt; - Assists with GDPR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stand Out&lt;/strong&gt; - Bring your site to life with animation, parallax backgrounds, and scroll effects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One-Click Deployment&lt;/strong&gt; - No servers. No databases. Only files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;color-themes&#34;&gt;Color Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;academia comes with &lt;strong&gt;day (light) and night (dark) mode&lt;/strong&gt; built-in. Click the sun/moon icon in the top right of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://academia-demo.netlify.com/&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt; to see it in action!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose a stunning color and font theme for your site. Themes are fully customizable and include:&lt;/p&gt;








  
  


&lt;div class=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;

  
  
  
  
    
    
    
    
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-gallery&#34; href=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-1950s.png&#34; data-caption=&#34;1950s&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-1950s_huaf5482f8cea0c5a703a328640e3b7509_21614_0x190_resize_lanczos_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
    
    
    
    
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-gallery&#34; href=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-apogee.png&#34; data-caption=&#34;Apogee&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-apogee_hu4b45d99db97150df01464c393bfd17d4_24119_0x190_resize_lanczos_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
    
    
    
    
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-gallery&#34; href=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-coffee-playfair.png&#34; data-caption=&#34;Coffee theme with Playfair font&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-coffee-playfair_hu446a8f670cc5622adcc77b97ba95f6c5_22462_0x190_resize_lanczos_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
    
    
    
    
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-gallery&#34; href=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-dark.png&#34; data-caption=&#34;Dark&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-dark_hu1e8601ecc47f58eada7743fdcd709d3d_21456_0x190_resize_lanczos_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
    
    
    
    
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-gallery&#34; href=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-default.png&#34; data-caption=&#34;Default&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-default_huba6228b7bdf30e2f03f12ea91b2cba0d_21751_0x190_resize_lanczos_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
    
    
    
    
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-gallery&#34; href=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-forest.png&#34; data-caption=&#34;Forest&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-forest_hu4f093a1c683134431456584193ea41ee_21797_0x190_resize_lanczos_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
    
    
    
    
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-gallery&#34; href=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-ocean.png&#34; data-caption=&#34;Ocean&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-ocean_hu14831ccafc2219f30a7a096fa7617e01_21760_0x190_resize_lanczos_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
    
    
    
    
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-gallery&#34; href=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-strawberry.png&#34; data-caption=&#34;Strawberry&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://jerad.xyz/post/snail/gallery/theme-strawberry_hu36b0b347fcca08bd39e2df22dcedbdfb_39532_0x190_resize_lanczos_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  

  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ecosystem&#34;&gt;Ecosystem&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sourcethemes/academia-admin&#34;&gt;academia Admin&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; An admin tool to import publications from BibTeX or import assets for an offline site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sourcethemes/academia-scripts&#34;&gt;academia Scripts&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Scripts to help migrate content to new versions of academia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;install&#34;&gt;Install&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can choose from one of the following four methods to install:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/install/#install-with-web-browser&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;one-click install using your web browser (recommended)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/install/#install-with-git&#34;&gt;install on your computer using &lt;strong&gt;Git&lt;/strong&gt; with the Command Prompt/Terminal app&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/install/#install-with-zip&#34;&gt;install on your computer by downloading the &lt;strong&gt;ZIP files&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/install/#install-with-rstudio&#34;&gt;install on your computer with &lt;strong&gt;RStudio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/get-started/&#34;&gt;personalize and deploy your new site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;updating&#34;&gt;Updating&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/update/&#34;&gt;View the Update Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to &lt;em&gt;star&lt;/em&gt; the project on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academia/&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; to help keep track of &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/updates&#34;&gt;updates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;license&#34;&gt;License&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2016-present &lt;a href=&#34;https://georgecushen.com&#34;&gt;George Cushen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Released under the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academia/blob/master/LICENSE.md&#34;&gt;MIT&lt;/a&gt; license.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
