<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>story time on Jerad&#39;s place</title>
    <link>https://jerad.xyz/categories/story-time/</link>
    <description>Recent content in story time on Jerad&#39;s place</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 17:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://jerad.xyz/categories/story-time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Media Concept</title>
      <link>https://jerad.xyz/project/new-world-media/concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerad.xyz/project/new-world-media/concept/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-media-story-telling&#34;&gt;New Media Story Telling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stories play out on multiple mediums such as audio podcast, written web and mobile app, broadcast, soular spectrum. Content strategy set to optimize consumer participation and engagement as well as lifestyle (&lt;strong&gt;pronouns:&lt;/strong&gt; embodied experiencer / viewer / consumer).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-way----a-level-one-culture&#34;&gt;The Way &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; A &amp;ldquo;Level-One&amp;rdquo; Culture&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way was a methodology by which a small group of individuals could incept social progress and subconscious healing.&lt;br&gt;
A planet becomes level-one when it is completely self sufficients. All the worlds necessary energy is harvested from itself by means such as heat energy from volcanic sources, wind and tide energy. Waiste and recycling is done in such a manner that the planet does not develop an excess rate which would consume more land over time and food is produced at a rate sufficient to provide the entire population with a nutritional diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-way-was-the-idea-of&#34;&gt;The way was the idea of:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using a select group of zeitgeist sensitive individuals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who would travel together to feel for the subconscious activity of a given population&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The measurement taken would be experienced and studied&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some target or desired zeitgeist or desired direction would be agreed upon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The group would meditate on what was needed in order make the social conscious or subconscios progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
